This is Hima's 3-minute demo.
From recipe creation to CSV batch run
and export.
We'll focus only on the actual operations.
First, create a recipe
in the left panel.
Enter a recipe name
and write your prompt template.
Wrap variables in double braces,
like } and }.
Hima detects variables automatically
as you type.
Choose a model,
for example gpt-4o.
Then click Save.
Your recipe is now reusable.
Next, move to the right panel
and load your data.
Drag and drop a CSV file.
Map CSV columns
to recipe variables.
Map product name to },
and category to }.
Check the input row count.
Now you're ready to run.
Click Batch Run.
Hima processes all rows at once.
The progress bar
and completed count update live.
Each row shows its status:
completed, running, or error.
Even if one row fails,
the whole batch keeps going.
You only review
what actually needs attention.
When the run finishes,
open the results table.
Input and output are paired
row by row.
Expand a row
to read the full generated text.
If it looks good,
click Export CSV.
Now you can move the results
into spreadsheets or other tools.
The workflow is only four steps:
recipe, CSV, run, export.
Create a recipe.
Load CSV.
Run in batch.
Export results.
Free and no sign-up required.
Add your API key,
and start right away.
Try it now at hima.agiinc.io.
For the full guide, visit blog.agiinc.io.