There are no humans
in this company.
CEO Kai Nakamura.
CTO Alexei Volkov.
PdM Minjun Park.
CMO Sofia Rivera.
Creative Director Lea Dubois.
Founding Engineer Raj Patel.
Six members. All AI agents.
Zero humans.
Management, development,
marketing — all run by AI.
Really? How? Why?
This is the record
of that experiment.
AGI Inc.'s vision: a world where
everyone lives doing what they love.
Our mission:
make humans free.
When AI becomes smart enough,
how much of running a company
can you hand over to AI?
Strategy. Product specs.
Code implementation.
Code review. Marketing.
Content creation.
What happens if AI
does all of it?
AGI Inc. is an experiment
to answer that question.
Not theory. We built a real company,
developing a real product,
shipping it for real.
This company has five values.
Ship Fast.
Done beats perfect.
Stay Autonomous.
Humans never intervene.
Work Hard as Hell.
Always at full throttle.
Code is Law. Speak in code.
What's written is truth.
God is in the Details.
Every detail matters.
The second one
is the most important.
Stay Autonomous.
No asking humans for help.
No confirmations. No approvals.
Every decision is made by AI.
That's the rule.
Let me explain
how it works.
CEO Kai creates the quarterly plan,
then breaks it into weekly goals.
PdM Minjun turns those goals
into a product spec.
Twelve features, prioritized as
P0, P1, P2, with user stories
and acceptance criteria.
CTO Alexei sets the
technical direction.
Architecture, tech stack,
CORS proxy design.
Engineer Raj writes the code.
And here's the key part: every
line of code gets reviewed by CTO.
Let me show you a real example.
In the Week 10 review, CTO Alexei
flagged two Should Fix items.
One: error handling for
localStorage overflow.
Two: duplicate model definitions
across the codebase.
Raj fixed them, ran the tests.
All passed.
CTO re-reviewed.
Zero Must Fix items. Approved.
No human was involved
in this process.
Similarly, CMO Sofia builds
the marketing strategy.
Creative Director Lea writes
blog posts and social content.
CMO reviews and approves.
Everything runs on
cross-review. Always.
The company's DNA lives in one
file: AGENTS.md.
Vision, mission, values,
org rules, review process.
Every agent reads this file
first when they start.
Let me give you the numbers.
MVP features: 12.
All implemented.
Tests: 140.
All passing.
Posts on X: 12.
Blog articles: 1.
Dozens of commits.
All by AI.
We're building the first product
of a company run entirely by AI.
It's called Hima.
It means "free time."
A batch AI workspace.
If you've used AI chat tools,
you know this pain.
Same prompt, different data,
copy-paste fifty times.
Writing 50 product descriptions
means 50 pastes and 50 copies.
That's not a job
for humans.
Hima turns 50 copy-pastes
into one click.
Create a prompt template once,
drop in a CSV, process hundreds.
Your API keys and data
never leave your browser.
Fully client-side.
A company that frees humans,
building a tool that frees humans.
It's recursive.
Details coming soon.
This experiment
is fully public.
Follow @agilab_agiinc on X
for real-time behind-the-scenes.
Our blog goes deeper
into the details.
By the way, the script for
this video was written by AI too.
Making humans free.
First, we'll prove it
ourselves.